
<source>
  <jobs_count>5</jobs_count>
  <generation_time>2021-10-15 12:17:00 +0300</generation_time>
  <jobs>
    <job>
      <title>Real Estate Agent -- Full Time Position</title>
      <url>https://www.hiringcenterjobs.com/Mcc/pmz/pmz-2021727-5108594.htm</url>
      <job_reference>pmz-2021727-5108594.htm</job_reference>
      <location>Ceres, CA  95307</location>
      <country></country>
      <city>Ceres</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip_code>95307</zip_code>
      <req_number></req_number>
      <posted_at></posted_at>
      <company>PMZ Real Estate</company>
      <body>Job DescriptionThe Real Estate Agent is a key position in any Real Estate organization. By attracting, interacting with, and networking with both sellers and buyers, Real Estate Agents facilitate housing transactions in and around their communities. Because of the independent nature of the job, an opportunistic and proactive attitude is needed for success in the Real Estate Agent career field. The Real Estate career field is best suited to proactive, independent thinking, and achievement focused individuals.Real Estate Agents are unique in how they are paid. As an Agent, your compensation is tied directly to performance. The more transactions you facilitate, the more compensation you will earn. This put your in control of your earning potential. It's not unusual for a Real Estate Agent to be earning over $100,000 after a few years of hard-work.Regulatory Notice: While a real estate license is not required to apply, you must obtain a real estate license before officially being hired. To earn a real estate license you will need to complete real estate classes (online or in-person) offered by an accredited learning institution and pass a state licensing exam. To learn more about the real estate licensing process, apply now and our recruiting team will provide additional details.Job ResponsibilitiesNetwork with customers via phone, email, and social mediaEducate clients on the state of the real estate marketDistribute information concerning buying and selling real estateAnswer questions about contracts and terms of saleUtilize computer technology to manage a database of customers and prospectsAssist potential clients with financial decisions concerning real estateResolve conflicts that arise during the purchase or sale of real estate propertyAbout PMZ Real EstatePMZ Real Estate is the #1 real estate firm in the market and is the 38th largest real estate firm in the United States. Our agents sell over $1.2 billion dollars in Central Valley real estate annually. PMZ also has the leading online real estate presence in the Central Valley and has been named one of the top 10 real estate brokerage websites in the United States. With thousands of buyer visits each day and millions of hits each month, PMZ's online solutions give our clients an unparalleled edge over the competition.Working HereIf you're looking to start your real estate career in the right place, put PMZ at the top of your list. We are one of nine companies (and the only real estate company) recently selected as a "Best Places to Work" in the Central Valley. The "Best Places to Work" is a national competition that evaluates companies based on indicators such as wages, benefits, company culture and employee feedback. Brighten your future by connecting your talents with the best real estate team in the Central Valley!Our Equal Opportunity PromiseWe are committed to fair hiring practices and operate as an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, sexual orientation, age, marital status, religion, or nation of origin. We pride ourselves as being exceptional leaders and members of our community and we're committed to treating all our potential employees with the same level of care and respect.IndustryReal Estate</body>
    </job>
    <job>
      <title>Real Estate Professional</title>
      <url>https://www.hiringcenterjobs.com/Mcc/pmz/pmz-2021823-9195807.htm</url>
      <job_reference>pmz-2021823-9195807.htm</job_reference>
      <location>Lodi, CA  95242</location>
      <country></country>
      <city>Lodi</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip_code>95242</zip_code>
      <req_number></req_number>
      <posted_at></posted_at>
      <company>PMZ Real Estate</company>
      <body>Job DescriptionAs a Real Estate Professional, you will be responsible for facilitating interaction between buyers and sellers of Real Estate. This requires not only good administrative skills, but also a charismatic personality. Real Estate organizations are searching for proactive, self-managing, individuals who have a desire to provide the best possible experience for the customer. The Real Estate Professional position is geared to people who are driven by personal achievement, able to self-manage, and able to manage large networks of customers and prospects.Compensation for Real Estate Agents is based on commissions. This means that as you help buy and sell more property, your income will grow. Now is a great time to get involved in this industry. Real Estate Agents who excel can earn over $100,000 a year after they've built a client base. The more work you put into establishing a client base, the more money you will earn.Regulatory Notice: While a real estate license is not required to apply, you must obtain a real estate license before officially being hired. To earn a real estate license you will need to complete real estate classes (online or in-person) offered by an accredited learning institution and pass a state licensing exam. To learn more about the real estate licensing process, apply now and our recruiting team will provide additional details.Job ResponsibilitiesBuild strong, sustainable relationships with existing client contacts and establish new contacts through networking.Demonstrate knowledge and experience of all aspects of digital marketing and delivery.Show desire to forge connections, build trust and manage long-term relationships with individuals.Prepare documents such as representation contracts, purchase agreements, closing statements, deeds and leases.Utilize web-based tools to manage a database of customers and prospects.Assist potential clients with fiscal decisions concerning real estate.Resolve disagreements/issues that arise during the purchase or sale of real estate property.About PMZ Real EstatePMZ Real Estate is the #1 real estate firm in the market and is the 38th largest real estate firm in the United States. Our agents sell over $1.2 billion dollars in Central Valley real estate annually. PMZ also has the leading online real estate presence in the Central Valley and has been named one of the top 10 real estate brokerage websites in the United States. With thousands of buyer visits each day and millions of hits each month, PMZ's online solutions give our clients an unparalleled edge over the competition.Working HereIf you're looking to start your real estate career in the right place, put PMZ at the top of your list. We are one of nine companies (and the only real estate company) recently selected as a "Best Places to Work" in the Central Valley. The "Best Places to Work" is a national competition that evaluates companies based on indicators such as wages, benefits, company culture and employee feedback. Brighten your future by connecting your talents with the best real estate team in the Central Valley!Our Equal Opportunity PromiseWe are committed to fair hiring practices and operate as an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, sexual orientation, age, marital status, religion, or nation of origin. We pride ourselves as being exceptional leaders and members of our community and we're committed to treating all our potential employees with the same level of care and respect.IndustryReal Estate</body>
    </job>
    <job>
      <title>Licensed Real Estate Professional</title>
      <url>https://www.hiringcenterjobs.com/Mcc/pmz/pmz-2021727-8337839.htm</url>
      <job_reference>pmz-2021727-8337839.htm</job_reference>
      <location>Ceres, CA  95307</location>
      <country></country>
      <city>Ceres</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip_code>95307</zip_code>
      <req_number></req_number>
      <posted_at></posted_at>
      <company>PMZ Real Estate</company>
      <body>Job DescriptionThe real estate industry is booming with excitement right now. We are looking for a Licensed Real Estate Professional who can offer their creativity, problem-solving skills and marketing ideas to our team. As a Licensed Real Estate Professional, you are a key player in a real estate transaction. You will walk your clients through every aspect of their home purchase or sale. This involves researching the current real estate market and finding ways to help your clients' homes stand out as unique and desirable.The ideal candidate for this Licensed Real Estate Professional position has a passion for customer service and creativity. A background in sales, marketing and customer service is an asset, along with your real estate license. We will provide training to help you develop those skills and grow your potential. The ability to be a self-starter and to take initiative to create a broad and loyal client base is essential to this role.Compensation in the real estate market is directly tied to a Real Estate Professional's performance. There is reasonable potential to make over $100,000 a year. You will find that the more time and work you put into establishing your client base through networking and referrals, the more income you will earn for yourself.Regulatory Notice: While a real estate license is not required to apply, you must obtain a real estate license before officially being hired. To earn a real estate license you will need to complete real estate classes (online or in-person) offered by an accredited learning institution and pass a state licensing exam. To learn more about the real estate licensing process, apply now and our recruiting team will provide additional details.Job ResponsibilitiesIn this role, you will...Stay informed on the local real estate market so you can offer sound advice to clients on how to best market and price their homeNetwork and market your real estate professional services to help grow your client baseRepresent your clients' best interests during negotiations and contract write-upsEstablish positive relationships with other real estate professionals in the communityBe available to your clients to answer all questions and provide solutions throughout every step of their real estate transaction experienceComplete relevant training to keep yourself informed and relevant within the current real estate marketBe available to show client's homes and attend open housesCome up with creative solutions for making you and your real estate portfolio stand out in the current marketAs a broker, we will...Provide an environment of healthy work/life balance that offers you flexibilityOffer a positive work culture of mutual support, encouragement and respectCoach you through the licensing process and provide training and career development opportunitiesShare our branding and technology to help you establish credibility and trust in the marketto the general public.About PMZ Real EstatePMZ Real Estate is the #1 real estate firm in the market and is the 38th largest real estate firm in the United States. Our agents sell over $1.2 billion dollars in Central Valley real estate annually. PMZ also has the leading online real estate presence in the Central Valley and has been named one of the top 10 real estate brokerage websites in the United States. With thousands of buyer visits each day and millions of hits each month, PMZ's online solutions give our clients an unparalleled edge over the competition.Working HereIf you're looking to start your real estate career in the right place, put PMZ at the top of your list. We are one of nine companies (and the only real estate company) recently selected as a "Best Places to Work" in the Central Valley. The "Best Places to Work" is a national competition that evaluates companies based on indicators such as wages, benefits, company culture and employee feedback. Brighten your future by connecting your talents with the best real estate team in the Central Valley!Our Equal Opportunity PromiseWe are committed to fair hiring practices and operate as an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, sexual orientation, age, marital status, religion, or nation of origin. We pride ourselves as being exceptional leaders and members of our community and we're committed to treating all our potential employees with the same level of care and respect.IndustryReal Estate Lic</body>
    </job>
    <job>
      <title>Licensed Real Estate Sales Agent</title>
      <url>https://www.hiringcenterjobs.com/Mcc/pmz/pmz-2021823-4209900.htm</url>
      <job_reference>pmz-2021823-4209900.htm</job_reference>
      <location>Lodi, CA  95242</location>
      <country></country>
      <city>Lodi</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip_code>95242</zip_code>
      <req_number></req_number>
      <posted_at></posted_at>
      <company>PMZ Real Estate</company>
      <body>Job DescriptionThe Licensed Real Estate Sales Agent is a position well-suited for a personable and customer service oriented individual. You'll be responsible for walking various clients through one of the most substantial transactions they will ever make. This career is multi-faceted and offers the agent the opportunity to act as a sales professional, marketing expert, customer service manager, contract negotiator and client advocate. Every day in real estate is new, exciting, and different than the previous day, so the Licensed Real Estate Sales Agent must be extremely flexible and thrive in a rapidly changing environment.To fulfill this role as a Real Estate Sales Agent, you will need to be self-driven and perform well under pressure. This role also affords significant flexibility, so you'll need to be able to work independently and stay on task in order to meet clients' needs. Real Estate Agents need a loyal client roster in order to be effective, so strong customer service is essential. If you possess these traits and have your real estate license, then we want to speak with you.Compensation for Real Estate Agents is commission-based. This means that the more inventory you move, the more income you will generate for yourself. The real estate industry is ever-evolving. Now is a great time to get involved. Many agents can earn over $100,000 a year once they have established their business.Regulatory Notice: While a real estate license is not required to apply, you must obtain a real estate license before officially being hired. To earn a real estate license you will need to complete real estate classes (online or in-person) offered by an accredited learning institution and pass a state licensing exam. To learn more about the real estate licensing process, apply now and our recruiting team will provide additional details.Job ResponsibilitiesAs a Licensed Real Estate Sales Agent, you will...Work closely with clients to identify properties that meet their criteriaCultivate rapport with potential buyers and assist with their home buying needsCreate and distribute marketing materials that advertise your real estate sales services in your communityMarket your real estate agent services to the local communityAdvocate for clients during sales negotiationsCommunicate in a timely manner with all clients who are active in the real estate sales process and follow up and reach out to those who are notFollow up with clients after their transactionNetwork and pursue referrals and nurture a roster of clientsAs a broker, we will...Coach you through the licensing process for becoming a real estate agentEquip you with training and support for best practices within our local real estate marketProvide you with the flexibility to plan your own schedule so you can have a healthy work/life balanceOffer you a competitive commission rateAbout PMZ Real EstatePMZ Real Estate is the #1 real estate firm in the market and is the 38th largest real estate firm in the United States. Our agents sell over $1.2 billion dollars in Central Valley real estate annually. PMZ also has the leading online real estate presence in the Central Valley and has been named one of the top 10 real estate brokerage websites in the United States. With thousands of buyer visits each day and millions of hits each month, PMZ's online solutions give our clients an unparalleled edge over the competition.Working HereIf you're looking to start your real estate career in the right place, put PMZ at the top of your list. We are one of nine companies (and the only real estate company) recently selected as a "Best Places to Work" in the Central Valley. The "Best Places to Work" is a national competition that evaluates companies based on indicators such as wages, benefits, company culture and employee feedback. Brighten your future by connecting your talents with the best real estate team in the Central Valley!Our Equal Opportunity PromiseWe are committed to fair hiring practices and operate as an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, sexual orientation, age, marital status, religion, or nation of origin. We pride ourselves as being exceptional leaders and members of our community and we're committed to treating all our potential employees with the same level of care and respect.IndustryReal Estate Lic</body>
    </job>
    <job>
      <title>Real Estate Agent -- Entry-Level</title>
      <url>https://www.hiringcenterjobs.com/Mcc/pmz/pmz-2021823-2453238.htm</url>
      <job_reference>pmz-2021823-2453238.htm</job_reference>
      <location>Lodi, CA  95242</location>
      <country></country>
      <city>Lodi</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip_code>95242</zip_code>
      <req_number></req_number>
      <posted_at></posted_at>
      <company>PMZ Real Estate</company>
      <body>Job DescriptionA Real Estate Agent plays an essential role in a real estate transaction. In this role, you will advocate for your clients by understanding their preferences, representing them when negotiating a sale and assisting them with every detail of their home purchase and sale. Real estate is an exciting industry that is constantly evolving, and we need someone who is creative, enthusiastic and willing to think outside of the box to give their clients the best real estate experience possible.You would fit this role as an Entry-Level Real Estate Agent if you love to come up with creative solutions to make yourself stand out in a thriving real estate market. As this is an entry-level position, prior real estate experience is not required. We will provide you with training and resources to prepare you to become a successful agent. Real Estate offers a lot of independence, so if you are a self-starter and enjoy flexibility, this position could be a good fit for you.Real Estate Agents receive compensation based on their transaction volume. When a sale or purchase is achieved, you will receive a competitive commission. The more sales you close, the more commission you earn. Real Estate Agents often earn more than $100,000 a year, but it can take a couple years to reach that goal as you build your client portfolio.Regulatory Notice: While a real estate license is not required to apply, you must obtain a real estate license before officially being hired. To earn a real estate license you will need to complete real estate classes (online or in-person) offered by an accredited learning institution and pass a state licensing exam. To learn more about the real estate licensing process, apply now and our recruiting team will provide additional details.Job ResponsibilitiesAs a Real Estate Agent, you will...Help clients price their property and get it ready to put on the marketStay updated on your local real estate market so you can offer clients an accurate comparison of home sales in their areaArrange home showings and open housesAdvertise your real estate services to the local communityRepresent your clients' best interests during contract negotiationsCommunicate with clients regularly and check in on their needsCreate marketing strategies so clients can sell their home quickly and profitablyDevelop strategies to obtain referrals and build your client portfolioAs a broker, we will... Walk you through the process of obtaining a real estate licenseAfter obtaining your license, we offer training, resources and support to help you become the best real estate agent you can beAccommodate a flexible work schedule to help you establish a healthy work/life balanceOffer competitive compensation ratesAbout PMZ Real EstatePMZ Real Estate is the #1 real estate firm in the market and is the 38th largest real estate firm in the United States. Our agents sell over $1.2 billion dollars in Central Valley real estate annually. PMZ also has the leading online real estate presence in the Central Valley and has been named one of the top 10 real estate brokerage websites in the United States. With thousands of buyer visits each day and millions of hits each month, PMZ's online solutions give our clients an unparalleled edge over the competition.Working HereIf you're looking to start your real estate career in the right place, put PMZ at the top of your list. We are one of nine companies (and the only real estate company) recently selected as a "Best Places to Work" in the Central Valley. The "Best Places to Work" is a national competition that evaluates companies based on indicators such as wages, benefits, company culture and employee feedback. Brighten your future by connecting your talents with the best real estate team in the Central Valley!Our Equal Opportunity PromiseWe are committed to fair hiring practices and operate as an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, sexual orientation, age, marital status, religion, or nation of origin. We pride ourselves as being exceptional leaders and members of our community and we're committed to treating all our potential employees with the same level of care and respect.IndustryReal Estate Nexp</body>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</source>
